[♪ intriguing music playing]
[Noel] We set out on a journey…
into the American Southwest…
to return to where it all began.
[♪ music fades]
Agreed?
-Agreed!
[narrator] After completing
six months of training in Los Angeles,
the all-boy music group, Travis Japan,
spreads its wings and soars,
not only in Japan
but also the global music scene.
This is their journey
across the Southwestern United States.
Putting his tour guide certification
to use,
Noel prepared two travel plans
for the members.
Everyone except Noel will divide up
into two groups and go on road trips.
[both laugh]
[narrator] The members travel
through the Southwestern United States
as they experience the rich culture
and vast expanse of the Wild West.
What are Noel's goals?
[Umi] I wonder what sort of things
-Noel has planned for us.
-This is the most photogenic spot.
[Shime] The river is pretty too.
It's been a while! [laughs] Yeah!
Long time no see!
[narrator] Following Noel's travel guide…
[no audible dialogue]
…the members discover
a horizon they've never seen
at the end of the ten-day,
1,000-kilometer trip.
[♪ upbeat music playing]
Travis Japan:
SUMMER VACATION!! in the USA
[narrator, in Japanese]
July 2025, Narita Airport.
-[Shime] Here.
-The seven members of Travis Japan are
checking in for their flight
to Los Angeles.
We're all set. Yes.
Thank you. [speaks indistinctly]
Here we come.
Let's get this party started.
[Chaka] Hey, got yours?
What's your seat number?
I got a great one. That's personal info.
-Show me.
-It's private.
[Machu] Hey, no.
[exhales sharply]
-Nice.
-We're done checking in.
-We're all checked in.
-We're ready.
[♪ upbeat music playing]
Hiya.
All right.
Whoa.
-[Genta] Hello.
-[Machu, in English] Hey.
-[in Japanese] Here we go.
-Oh.
-[member speaks indistinctly]
-[Machu, Genta laugh]
[narrator] Noel gives the members
a rundown of their itineraries
at the airport lounge.
Travis Japan was approved
for a ten-day vacation!
-[Genta] Whoa!
-What? Seriously? You're not kidding?
I organized a special trip
you're sure to love.
Let's have a blast
on this ten-day summer getaway!
-Hooray!
-Isn't this great?
This is huge. Huge.
[narrator]
This special summer break Noel organized
for the Travis Japan members
is a road trip
through the Southwestern United States.
The arid landscape surrounding
the Rocky Mountains is home
to an America the members have yet to see.
The Travis Japan members will divide
into two groups
and drive separately toward
their final destination: Sedona, Arizona.
Team A is made up of
Chaka, Umi, and Shizu.
They will set out
from Salt Lake City, Utah,
and explore America's wilderness
in a rented RV.
Team B includes Shime, Genta, and Machu.
They will embark from Albuquerque,
New Mexico, in a rental car.
Their itinerary focuses on discovering
the Wild West culture tucked away
in rural towns.
Noel will be in Sedona ahead of everyone
to prepare for the other members
to arrive.
-Yo.
-This is great.
-It's free for us, right?
-That's what's up.
I have one question though.
Noel, what will you be up to?
[Genta] Oh, that's a great point. Yeah.
[Noel] Ah. [mutters]
-I will wait for your arrival in Sedona.
-[Shime, Genta, Chaka] Sedona?
If this is California,
then Nevada and Las Vegas are over here.
There's a neighboring state
that's kind of below those places,
and to the east
is a famous city called Sedona.
That's where I'll be waiting.
[Shime, in English] I see.
[in Japanese] You'll be waiting?
[Noel] I will be
-in special training.
-Training?
-You're going to train?
-Wait.
-You have to train by yourself?
-[laughs]
I want the most memorable part
to be when we're together again.
To make that happen,
I need to be in Sedona before you.
That tracks.
You'll tell us
what you've been up to then?
Team A's leader, Chaka.
-Here.
-[Shime] Oh.
-Sure you're ready?
-Leader.
-This is for you.
-Thank you.
-Don't misplace it.
-Well then.
Team B's leader, Shime.
-Oh! Thanks.
-Thank you.
-Don't lose them, guys.
-I might.
[Shime, Noel laugh]
-Well…
-I'm sure you'll find your way without it.
[Genta muttering]
[Chaka] Is that the travel plans?
-Your itineraries.
-Here you go.
[Noel] You don't have to follow it to a T.
You can feel it out
and choose your own adventure.
[Shime] Okay.
Well, if you follow this planner,
you'll have fun regardless.
[Genta] Thanks.
You made these just for us?
[members] Thank you. Thanks, man. Thanks.
[PA chimes]
[♪ gentle country music playing]
-Time to depart.
-Whoa, time to head out.
-Bye.
-Off we go.
-See you.
Bye-bye.
See you.
[♪ upbeat country music playing]
-Hello.
-Hey.
-Thank you for choosing to fly with us.
-Next one over.
Dang it, we're a bit far.
-I'll miss you.
-[Chaka mutters]
Comes with body lotion and lip balm.
No way.
[no audible dialogue]
Oh.
We have summer vacation
to look forward to on top of these seats.
This is the best.
This is where it all begins.
Having time to relax is important too.
I'm really grateful.
[♪ upbeat country music continues]
[♪ music ends]
[Travis Japan singing in Japanese]
[narrator] Travis Japan is a dance-vocal
group that shine on the global stage.
There are seven members. Chaka.
Umi.
Shime.
Noel.
Shizu.
Genta.
And Machu.
After completing training in Los Angeles,
they made their global debut in 2022.
They enchant their fans across the globe.
Continuing to captivate fans globally
with their incredible performances
and teamwork.
-[in English] The show was amazing.
-Amazing. It was really, really good.
It was a really good experience.
I would definitely do it again.
I am from Mexico,
but I really love your music.
And I learned Japanese.
-We love Chaka! [whoops]
-[chuckles]
My favorite's Machu.
[narrator, in Japanese]
After their massive success
on a popular American TV show,
Travis Japan broke through
from the domestic music scene
to the international stage.
[singing]
[narrator] With the international tour
concluding successfully,
2025 became the year the group
had the chance to go global.
It was exactly the time
for all the members
to enjoy a summer break together.
Secretly, Noel took his break before
the others in order to prepare a surprise.
[in English] Union Station, Los Angeles.
[♪ upbeat music playing]
Oh.
[♪ music ends]
[indistinct announcement on PA]
[in Japanese]
Never thought I'd see the day
when I board an Amtrak
to travel to all sorts of places.
That's another big item
off my bucket list.
I want to go to all kinds of places
and see all sorts of things.
Come in contact with the unknown,
experience new things.
By the time this journey ends,
I hope I've grown a bit wiser.
[♪ upbeat music playing]
Because I love to travel,
I got certified as a tour guide.
That's what inspired me
to plan everyone's summer vacation.
And I thought, it should be America.
It's where we got our start, after all.
[horn blasts]
[Noel] From Los Angeles,
I board the Southwest Chief train,
which runs on a transcontinental
railway service called Amtrak.
This route departs from Los Angeles
and cuts through the American Southwest.
I've always had an interest in traveling
and world geography,
but never took the initiative
to learn more.
I studied to become an expert
in this field.
I credit Travis Japan and its members
for inspiring me to get certified.
I can honestly say they pushed me
to study in my free time.
It's all thanks to them.
If I can plan a trip for the members
in return, I'd be over the moon.
And if they enjoy it, then even better.
[narrator, in English]
Las Vegas, New Mexico.
[Noel, in Japanese]
My first stop is Las Vegas.
But this isn't the Las Vegas you all know
with dazzling lights and casinos.
This Las Vegas is in New Mexico.
It was a famous hub
in the days of the Old West.
I bet they won't expect this.
This time, the most important thing is
for everyone to thoroughly enjoy the trip.
I'm interested in seeing
the members grow and learn
as they search and discover new things.
Also, I want to share their journey
with a lot of people.
This is what I can contribute
to Travis Japan.
I can use my certification
to plan a fun trip for them.
That's what I set out to do.
I hope the members enjoy my debut work…
[chuckles] …as a travel guide.
These are coasters.
Bet Machu would like them.
[chuckles]
Also, I wanted to get presents
to give out at the end.
Nothing expensive, more like tokens
of what this trip means to me.
Something really special.
That's when I stumbled upon this shop.
-[server, in English] Hey, welcome in.
-Hi.
-How's it going?
-I'm great and you?
-Good.
-I'm Noel.
Isaac. Nice to meet you. Yeah.
Do you have menu or something?
Ah, thank you.
-Well, here you are.
-Oh, thank you.
[in Japanese] Whoa, heaps.
[in English] Is it green chili fries?
[Isaac] These are the green chili fries,
this is the green chili pork,
a breakfast taco
and the Three Sisters taco.
-Okay, thanks so much.
-Enjoy.
Thank you.
[in Japanese] This is nuts.
The Southwestern United States was
a Mexican territory
until about 300 years ago.
To this day,
Mexican culture endures in this region.
Tacos are part of this Mexican culture.
Mmm.
Whoa.
So good.
Who knew tacos can be this delicious?
When I had these tacos, I just knew I had
to share them with the other members.
My favorite part about Travis Japan
is that we're a tight-knit group.
That's our strength, and also our appeal.
The unity among the seven of us
is what drives our day-to-day work.
If we can be just as united
when we're in groups of two or three,
then our teamwork
would be solidified even more.
That's what gave me the idea to divide up
the other members into two teams of three.
My plan was to come up with
an exciting ten-day summer break trip
and then prepare a surprise for them.
As I got to it,
I realized I needed to travel around
a little more on my own
and learn about the region.
I've decided to rent a car from Las Vegas
and drive around
the surrounding unfamiliar towns.
From there, I can pick a few spots
the members might like.
This makes me a bit nervous.
It's nerve-racking to drive such a big car
with the steering wheel on the left.
I don't have a good view of my right
and that throws me off a little.
I'm counting on you.
This is my first time driving
in the United States.
The other members will be driving
if things go accordingly.
So, maybe they'll feel the same way
when they're on the road.
[♪ upbeat music playing]
I was surprised by the size of the rental.
I didn't know driving
the wide roads of the United States
in a rental was this fun.
The members will enjoy it too.
I just know it.
[birds chirping]
[♪ funky music playing]
[narrator] Santa Fe, New Mexico.
[in Japanese] Santa Fe, New Mexico's
origins date back over 400 years.
This city predates
the founding of the United States.
It's a beautiful city
known as America's gem.
Whoa, this is amazing.
It gave me the urge
to learn more about America.
During training, we lived in Los Angeles,
but we also flew out to New York
and Chicago many times for work.
But there's still so much
I've yet to learn about this country.
Visit, see, touch, feel.
I wanted to get to the root
of the United States and take it all in.
[camera shutter clicking]
This area is home to the kinds of designs
and fashion that the members enjoy.
The unique blend of colonial Spain,
the Native culture, the Mexican Frontier
and the Old West gave rise
to the rich culture of this city.
You can see their influence
in jewelry too.
[♪ music ends]
[in English] Excuse me. May I ask you?
[clerk] Yeah, absolutely.
-May I try it?
-Yeah, absolutely. Please.
He's been doing jewelry
for quite some time.
-Really great guy.
-[in Japanese] Whoa, this is beautiful.
[in English]
So, this one has a lot of silver in it.
Jacques's one of our artists
that's more popular.
He's called a revivalist.
-And so-- Yeah.
-What? Vivalist? Oh.
So, he makes things
exactly how they would be made
in the late 1800s, early 1900s.
Also, the type of stone he used,
this looks to be Blue Gem turquoise
or possibly Royston.
-Mm-hmm.
-And so, that one is from Nevada.
It's really sought out after
and they're for that.
This one's by Dennis Hogan,
he's a local artist here.
-He actually lives in Santa Fe.
-[Noel] Uh-huh.
And, um, I'm biased 'cause he's my dad.
And so, he did this by hand.
And he made all the beads and things.
This one's 11,000.
11,000?
-Yes.
-11,000?
-Yep.
-[stutters] Are you kidding me?
-I know. Lots of silver here.
-[Noel chuckling]
Feel it, it's heavy.
It's a real--
It's a heavy, heavy necklace.
But it's one of my favorites.
It's so pretty.
[exclaims] May I try it?
[clerk] Yeah, please.
Whoa.
-[laughs]
-[clerk] It looks great.
-Thank you.
-[clerk] Look at you.
Wow. Ah. I'm so…
Ah. I'm so nervous.
[clerk] No, don't be. Don't be. It's okay.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
Cool. So cool.
My members must be interested in maybe,
uh, yeah. Absolutely.
They-They gonna love it.
-[clerk] Yeah, definitely.
-Yeah. Ooh.
[singer vocalizing]
Oh, they are cute.
[clerk] Thank you, it's great.
May I try? May I try something?
Yeah, go ahead. Try-Try them on.
See what you like.
So, how about this one?
Do you… So, let's try some on.
Okay. Where can I touch it?
-[clerk] Um, grab it wherever you like.
-Oh, here? Okay. Okay.
[clerk] Yeah, yeah.
Whoa.
-Super cool.
-[clerk] Right on. Yeah.
Or we can do, like, something different,
which is more, like, classier.
-Which is a white hat.
-Oh, yes.
-[clerk] And we also have, like…
-Oh.
…this one right here
where we've kind of, uh,
-burned, like, barbed wire into it.
-Oh!
[in Japanese] This is so cool.
Is this, uh, wool?
Yeah. So, it's gonna be wool.
And it's a mix of beaver in it.
Ooh.
[clerk] So, that's what we call
more of a fashion hat than a cowboy hat.
Oh. A cowboy hat.
Cowboy hat would be like…
Like, something like this…
-More regular, worn for work.
-Uh-huh.
[clerk] And a fashion hat would have
like, all the type of cool…
Oh.
-Something you can wear on a fashion show.
-Uh-huh.
Something to go out eating with.
So it's like…
[Noel, in Japanese] To start,
a ten-day summer break
is unheard of for us.
It may take years,
but I want Travis Japan
to grow into a group
with a strong sense of identity.
Then we can make the dreams of
current and future fans come true.
For us to achieve that, we need to develop
confidence that comes from within.
It's not enough to acquire certifications
and skills to tack onto our resumes.
It has to come from within.
We need to be deeply rooted in who we are
so that we can support ourselves.
What do we need right now
to grow like that?
What can we take in…
and what…
can we let go of?
That will be the key to our success.
[♪ playful music playing]
[Noel] It's summer break,
so it has to be fun.
But at the same time, I don't want them
to only visit famous spots.
I want this to be a journey
of self-discovery for the members.
A trip that'll give them a chance
to return to their beginnings.
[pump clicks]
[engine starts]
[♪ music ends]
What about somewhere
they can truly be themselves?
A place where they don't have
to cover up who they are.
Hot springs, huh?
[♪ gentle piano music playing]
[narrator, in English]
Pagosa Springs, Colorado.
[in Japanese] A tiny town nested
in the heart of the Rocky Mountains.
This natural hot spring is recognized
by the Guinness World Records
as the world's deepest geothermal spring.
In this town, time flows slowly
and nature offers healing.
[Noel] This looks to be a place
where they can bare their heart and body.
As I traveled around on my own,
a vision of the trip began to emerge.
They will group up into two teams
of three, Team A and Team B.
Team A will take in the magnificence
of Mother Nature on an RV trip.
Team B will set out on a cultural road
trip where they learn American history.
I also thought through
how to divide up the members.
This will be a trip everyone can enjoy.
Each member will take
back something different.
The final destination is Sedona, Arizona.
After a week of traveling,
all seven members will meet up in Sedona.
I've decided to wait for everyone
in Sedona,
where you can eat the tastiest tacos
in all of the United States.
And with that, I finished planning
Travis Japan's summer vacation.
[♪ music ends]
[♪ playful music plays]
[airplane engine whirs]
[narrator, in Japanese] Finally,
Travis Japan's summer vacation begins.
[in English] Salt Lake City, Utah.
[in Japanese] Team A will depart
from Salt Lake City to Sedona,
where Noel awaits.
[♪ upbeat music playing]
The first step for Team A members
Chaka, Umi, and Shizu
is to rent their transportation, an RV.
Whoa. Awesome, there it is.
Here it comes.
-Is that ours?
-Is that it?
Maybe that one.
-Are you gonna drive it?
-Guess I'll have to do.
[Umi] So for, what, the next week?
-We're gonna ride one of these.
-Aren't they kinda big?
-They've got a lot of different ones.
-[Umi] They're massive.
[Noel] Roads and horizons
stretching endlessly.
In the United States,
life on the road is a way of life.
Hit the road in an RV,
and today's landscapes,
deserts, forests,
and starry skies, become your home.
Pack up your freedom and hit the road.
That's the American RV life.
[Umi] Look, it's open.
-[Shizu] Look at the back.
-[Chaka] What's going on?
[Umi] Beats me.
Wait, you drive on the left side?
The driver's seat is on the left.
[Chaka] Crap, I can't remember
which side it is in Japan.
[Shizu] It's on the right.
[narrator]
Team A's designated driver is Chaka.
[Umi] Look, found more spots for sleeping.
[narrator] This is his first time driving
an American-sized vehicle.
-[Shizu] Is that my spot?
-[Umi] Yeah.
[Chaka] It's supposed to be
comfortable inside, right?
[Umi] There's a couch and even a sink.
-[Shizu] Whoa.
-[Chaka] This is some people's homes.
The driver's seat is separated.
This is crazy.
[Chaka]
It's like a studio apartment in here.
Oh, really?
-[Chaka] Awesome.
-There's a sleeping pod above too.
-You can sleep up there?
-That's what it seems like.
-Up there?
-[Umi] Wanna take a look inside?
[Shizu]
It's gonna reach 38 degrees Celsius.
-[Chaka, in English] Hi.
-Hi.
-My name's Daniel. All right.
This is your guys' RV.
Are you kidding?
My name is Chaka.
-All right. Hi.
-Nice to meet you. Good to see you.
Hi, my name is Umi.
-Umi?
-Yeah. Good to see you.
-I'm Shizu. Nice to meet you.
-Thank you so much.
-Yeah.
You guys ready to see your RV?
-[Umi] Yeah.
-[Chaka] Yes!
[Umi] Please.
All right, step right on in.
-All right. So this is your RV.
-[Chaka] Yeah. Mmm.
This is where you guys
can have your dinner.
-Eat your food.
-[Umi] Uh-huh.
And you can cook your food
right over here.
You got your stove and you got your sink.
You can run your water.
[Umi] Whoa! Wow!
And then your refrigerator.
Very important.
You'll be in the desert so you'll be…
-Very cold. That's your freezer. Yeah.
-Oh, really? Freezer?
For the ice?
-Uh-huh.
-[Chaka] Ice something.
[Umi] Whoa!
-So chilly. So cool.
-Yeah. Yeah, it gets really cold. Yeah.
So, and then here's your bed.
-Yeah.
-Bed?
And then, bed.
-[grunts]
-[Shizu laughs]
-Like that.
-Ah.
Comfortable.
[Chaka, in Japanese]
Got all the necessities.
-Right?
-[Umi] Doesn't this give you the itch
-to do something different?
-[Chaka] Like what?
-Hold a cookout competition using…
-[Shizu] Cookout?
…local ingredients and stuff.
-It's possible.
-Can't we?
-Can we use this? That's true.
-There's a stove here.
We buy ingredients
from a grocery store and cook.
[Umi] Hey, it's pretty comfy.
-Oh, look at this.
-[Shizu] This is amazing.
-There's even a toilet?
-It comes with a toilet.
-And a shower to boot.
-This is amazing.
[Shizu] Awesome.
[Chaka] You can shower on the road.
-[Umi] So if we get sweaty…
-[Chaka] Then we stop the car.
[Shizu] And take a shower.
-[in English] All right? Yeah.
-Sounds great.
All right, guys.
You're gonna have a lot of fun.
-Yes! Gonna have fun.
-[Chaka, in Japanese] Let's have a blast.
[♪ playful music playing]
[Shizu] How's being in the driver's seat?
How different is it?
[Chaka] Good question.
That's the ignition.
What's this?
[Umi] Try turning it on.
[Chaka] Can't find it.
-[Umi] No. Could be on the other side.
-[Shizu] Looking for the gears?
Doesn't look like it's up here.
[Chaka] It's in P.
[Shizu] I see it.
[Daniel, in English]
All right, so, right here,
you're gonna put the key in, turn that on.
This is where your, uh…
Basically right here
where you shift into drive.
-Oh, right. That's the shift lever.
-Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
Where's the side brake?
Your side brake is on the far left.
You're gonna take your foot
and press your foot and… to put that on.
-Oh, right.
-And then to release it
-there's a lever you pull.
-Uh-huh.
Pull that
and it'll pop that brake back out.
Oh, right.
So over here, you're gonna have
your wipers. See, you can twist.
It's the same one
that you use to change lanes.
-[Chaka] Oh.
-There you go, yeah.
So that's how you use your wiper.
[Shizu, in Japanese] Wouldn't it be
awesome to say you drive this thing?
[in English] Daniel, thank you.
-Thank you.
-[Daniel] Thank you, guys.
[♪ music ends]
[in Japanese] Yeah, it's cool.
It's just so big.
-It's huge.
-Okay, be honest.
-How do you feel about this?
-As the designated driver, well…
I prefer to take you guys
around in a much smaller car.
[Shizu laughs]
-Well, this time…
-[Shizu] We'll use this hunk of metal.
It's kinda big, but…
When else will I have the chance
to drive one of these?
Yeah, but… Rest assured,
I'll assist you from the passenger seat.
-Thanks.
-You can count on me.
I can make it as long as I got you.
Yeah. Although I'm not counting
on Shizuya to contribute much.
I'll watch over you from the back.
[Chaka] I like that we can take our time.
I love it.
We're taking on an entirely new challenge.
-[Shizu] Yeah. It's a new adventure.
-Yeah.
We get to experience nature in this car.
[Shizu] Can't get much better than this.
Is this the right car?
[Shizu] Yeah.
This RV's gonna take good care of us.
Thank you.
Let's say hi to it.
Let's say hello to the car.
Ready?
[all] Thanks for taking care of us.
It'll all work out.
Let's have a safe trip.
-Yeah.
-Let's do it.
[♪ upbeat music playing]
[narrator, in English]
Albuquerque, New Mexico.
[in Japanese] In this city, dry land,
blue skies and eclectic culture coexist.
Team B sets out
from Albuquerque towards Sedona.
-[Machu] Shall we get going?
-[Genta] Let's get rolling.
[Shime] Time for a road trip!
-Machu, the key.
-[Machu] Our first…
Can you be in charge of the key?
Machu, get in the passenger seat.
Oh, not the passenger seat.
Do you mind driving?
-Can you? Isn't this a cool car?
-[Machu] Super.
[narrator] Team B departs from here.
Team B members are
Shime, Genta, and Machu.
These three will drive to Sedona using
the same type of car as Noel.
-We're counting on you, leader.
-No objections about me being the leader?
Nope.
Not at all. You're the oldest.
I suppose that's true.
-Yeah.
-Hey, bro. Bro!
Bro? Guess you can consider me
your older brother.
We'll talk politely.
Seriously?
We're a team though. Let's just…
No, we should be respectful.
You're kidding, right? Don't be so formal.
-I'll drop it.
-Got it.
Wait, just like that? No pushback?
We don't even hold a license.
Yeah, that's true.
Machu, you're the only one
with an international license.
-Yep.
-We appreciate you.
Guess I'll do my best.
We owe you one.
If anything happens,
well, you've got a cheer squad.
-Thank you so much.
-[Machu laughs]
-I can navigate without drifting off.
-That'd be a big help.
We'll keep it entertaining.
Will you spot me if I signal?
-Leave it to us.
-[Shime] Yeah.
Since I'm in front, I can spot you.
Thanks. I'll watch for the rear.
-Okay.
-I'll do my best.
-Yeah.
-Before I forget.
Machu Picchu, got the camera?
-Oh, right. Here it is.
-So…
Is this yours?
Yeah, I brought it.
Do you wanna be the photographer?
Okay, I'll be in charge of driving
and taking pictures.
-It's nice.
-All right.
-I'm in charge…
-And
-Gen-chan.
-…of trying new things.
[chuckles]
Yeah, I'll dip my toes in anything
-that comes my way.
-[Machu] Sounds good.
[Shime] You're in charge of trying?
That's right.
I'll be the designated life of the party.
-I love it.
-Of course,
-we'll all enjoy ourselves.
-Sure.
You're gonna be hyped more than everyone.
-More than everyone else?
-I won't go overboard.
-[Machu laughs] Anyhow…
-[Shime laughs]
I'll be like
that one overly happy comedian. [chuckles]
Let's have Matsuda stay overly happy.
Let's make this a good trip for everyone.
-[Machu] Okay.
-Since I'm the oldest, I'll be the leader.
-Okay.
-Thanks. Thank you so much.
-Thank you.
-You just let me know if there's anything.
-Will do.
-Got it.
-Will you actually?
-Yeah.
-I'll come to you.
-Say, what was it…
Noel put together our itinerary.
-He handed it to me at the airport.
-That's right, he handed it to you.
-Right, right.
-[Shime] Here it is.
Oh, that's right.
-Here it is.
-That's it.
Travel plans. It's got everything
we need to know, right?
It'll tell us what to do.
Can you read it to us?
[Shime] Here's the first item.
Don't stutter now.
[Shime] Here it is.
"You will spend day one
of your summer break in transit."
-Okay.
-Great.
"I've booked a hotel in Las Vegas,
where I came up
-with the concept for this road trip."
-Wow!
-Las Vegas?
We get to go to Vegas?
"It's a really nice hotel.
Please enjoy the drive,
and have a wonderful night."
-We get to visit Vegas? Crazy!
-Great!
[Shime] That's what I'm talking about.
-[Genta] This is a proper summer vacation!
-[Shime] I'm stoked.
Remember, we stopped by Vegas
when we first came to the States.
[Shime] We did. We went together.
The dance competition was held in Vegas.
That's why we went.
We get to go back?
That's it, right?
It says, "Have a wonderful night."
-Maybe he booked us a show.
-Shows? Casinos?
-Casinos?
-Is this real?
Let's go!
[Chaka] All right! Well…
Time to open it up.
-[Umi] That's the notebook!
-Here it comes.
Noel's itinerary.
It looks familiar.
It's got all the destinations.
Let's take a look.
-That's his handwriting.
-We're Team A?
Team A!
[Umi] Whoa.
[all, in English]
"Do you know real America?"
[in Japanese]
"Do you know the real America?"
The United States we've come to know is…
What's it like?
-[Umi] We know LA?
-[Shizu] Just LA?
-We're about to find out.
-Got it.
[Chaka] Where are we going? "Day one."
[Umi] That's where we are.
[Chaka] From Salt Lake City…
The airport. We arrived in Salt Lake City.
-[Umi] Love the vibes.
-[Shizu] Cute arrow.
Then we'll head down to Moab.
-Moab.
-Moab, huh.
Utah, then?
-Utah.
-We have our destination.
[Shizu] Let's open up the map.
-We're not leaving Utah just yet.
-It's in Utah.
-[Shizu] Yeah.
-[Chaka] From Utah to Utah.
-Moab.
-Then…
Do you know where Utah is?
This is our current location.
Found it! We're in Salt Lake City.
-That's right.
-Right here.
-This is it!
-[Chaka] We're somewhere around here.
[Shizu] Moab…
[Chaka] Moab…
-There.
-[Chaka] Pocatello…
Pocatello.
-I found it!
-[Chaka] You did?
Is it pretty far?
-[Umi] I'd say, yeah.
-Moab? Where's Moab?
-There it is!
-Oh, that's it.
-Bingo!
-Tiny! Not what I expected.
-Is it here? Dang, that's far.
-Yeah.
There's quite a distance.
-Can we make it?
-Can you drive that much?
Well, we'll get there somehow.
-[laughs]
-Well, then…
-[Umi] Thanks.
-We have to get there though.
Yeah, I'll get us there.
[Umi] We're counting on you.
Wanna do our tradition
before we hit the road?
-Yeah!
-What tradition?
Do you know what he's talking about?
You know, our usual cheer.
-You don't know.
-That one.
We're apart from everyone, but… Yeah.
They aren't here,
but the other members must've done it too.
We've gotta do it.
-Okay then.
-Here.
-Then…
-Our hearts are one.
From Salt Lake City to Moab.
Yeah.
Safety first.
And as quickly as possible.
[in English] Yes, faster.
[in Japanese] Most importantly,
we'll have fun all the way to Moab.
Agreed?
[all] Agreed!
[♪ funky music playing]
[dashboard beeping]
-[Machu] Let's go!
-[Genta] Let's go!
[Shime] Let's go!
[Genta exclaims]
-You got it? To the left.
-Which way?
You got it.
It doesn't look bad at all.
-Yeah?
-Which way do I go?
-Maybe right.
-You sure it's not left?
-You're right. Right.
-No, right? Which way is it?
-The right?
-Or left?
[Machu]
Haven't touched a wheel in forever.
I'm kinda nervous.
Seriously, it's been a year or two.
-[Umi] Hey, Kaito.
-[Chaka] Should I start driving?
-[Umi] We're counting on you.
-[Shizu] You've got this!
Oh. It moved.
Nice!
We don't usually drive in Japan.
Not really.
[Umi] Whoo-hoo, here we go!
[Shizu] Whoa.
[applauding]
Good, you're doing great.
[Shizu] Yeah, you've got this.
[Shizu] You're driving on American roads! So cool.
[♪ funky music continues]
[♪ music ends]
Translated by Megumi Hunter